watervillegolflinks.ie 2018-05-10

# Privacy Statement — Experience Waterville Links

### Privacy Statement

This statement tells you about our privacy practices. It covers the collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Make be sure to read this entire Privacy Statement before using or submitting information to this site.

Consent

By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Statement. You consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Statement when you submit information to this site.

Personal data

Currently we only collect and hold your personal data if you complete a form or email us via an address on the Site. You can use this website without divulging any personal information.

Personal data held online, in hard copy form or in other electronic forms by Waterville Links Ltd for tracking, communicating with and servicing potential and actual customers.

If you do not want us to retain your contact information on our marketing database, please send an email to info@watervillelinks.ie.

Voluntary information

We may occasionally ask for further information about you to enable us to better provide you with appropriate services. You may at any time request that this information be removed from our database by writing toinfo@watervillelinks.ie.

Users may find out what personal information we hold about themselves on our database at any time, by writing to the above address. We reserve the right to charge an administration fee.

Collecting domain information

Waterville Links also collects domain information as part of its analysis of the use of this site. This data lets us better understand how customers are using the site. Waterville Links uses this information to improve the site. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part.

Cookies off

We reserve the right to use cookies to improve the experience of using this site. Cookies are small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. You should note that cookies cannot read data off your hard drive. Your web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.

Links

Where www.watervillegolflinks.ie/ contains links to other websites, Waterville Links is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other such sites. We encourage users to read the privacy statements of each site they link to that may collect personal data.

Other terms

Your use of this site is subject to our Terms & Conditions. Accessing this site constitutes agreement with those terms.

How to contact us

Waterville Links Ltd owns and operates this site. Contact us if you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Statement or the information practices of this site.

Waterville Links Ltd  
Waterville House  
Waterville  
Co. Kerry  
Ireland  
info@watervillelinks.ie  
www.watervillelinks.ie

Changes to Privacy Statement

Please accept this Privacy Statement as current. We reserve the right to change, modify or update this statement at any time without notice.
